Finding Aid for Residential College (University of Michigan) records, 1957-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Residential College (University of Michigan) records
1957-2011
University of Michigan. Residential College.
73.7 GB online
2 phonograph records
1 oversize folders
30 linear feet in 31 boxes
87319 Bimu 2 UAI
Inaugurated in 1967 as a living-learning community within the larger university, planning for the Residential College began in the early 1960s. Records relate to the planning and founding of the Residential College, 1962-1967, and include materials concerning curriculum, educational policies, governance and student attitudes from the College's opening in 1967 through 2010. Research papers produced by the Social Science Program's Student-Faculty Research Communities are also present
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Materials were received in July 2002 and 2007 from the Residential College (donor number 6754). Additional material came from former professor Don Brown (donor number 8894 ) in October 1999
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open without restriction, except for some files in box 31 and some online content.
The Residential College (RC) at the University of Michigan was inaugurated in 1967 as a living-learning community of teachers and students, to give participants an alternative to a large university experience. Early in the 1960s, the increasing enrollment in the university's College of Literature, Science and the Arts (LS&A) caused some members of the faculty to envision a school which combined the advantages of a small liberal arts college with a large research university. Dean (and later Vice President) Roger Heyns, Professor Theodore Newcomb, Professor Wilbert J. McKeachie, and LS&A Dean Burton Thuma were among the planners who worked to create the new college. The Residential College was officially established as a unit by the Regents in March 1964, and the Residential College Faculty Planning Committee was formed within LS&A in September 1964.
Dean Burton Thuma chaired the Planning Committee and was also named Director of the Residential College, although he retired before the first class of freshmen arrived in the fall of 1967. The Planning Committee prepared extensive reports to the faculty in 1965 and 1966, and, in April 1966, earned Regental approval of the Residential College concept and curriculum. The program was scheduled to begin in the East Quadrangle in the fall of 1967, with planners looking toward occupancy of a North Campus site in the fall of 1969. This latter part of the plan, which envisioned the college on a forty-acre site between Fuller Road and the Huron River, was eventually abandoned.
James Robertson became the director of the RC on July 1, 1967, and the first class of 217 freshmen matriculated in the fall. Key elements of the RC curriculum have endured from its beginnings: the freshman seminar, strong language proficiency and pass/fail grading, supplemented with textual evaluations. Early topics of concern within the community involved governance and the core curriculum. The inability of the RC to confer tenure was another difficult problem. Its powerlessness to reward instructors, coupled with financial instability, led to staffing problems. The result was such that the majority of classes were taught by teaching fellows or lecturers.
In the fall of 1971, LS&A Dean Frank Rhodes appointed a special committee to review the RC. Professor Rhoads Murphey chaired the committee, which produced its report in the spring of 1972. Although the report was often critical, it ended by affirming the goals and future of the RC. The LS&A faculty debated the Murphey report in October 1972. The outcomes were that a joint RC/LS&A Board should be established, and that the RC should be reviewed every four years. Crucial issues of financing and staffing were left unresolved.
Louis Orlin took over as acting director of the RC on July 1, 1973, and served for one year, though poor health greatly inhibited his work. He was succeeded by physics professor Marc Ross, who served for three years beginning July 1, 1974, and John Mersereau, Jr., who served for eight years beginning July 1, 1977. Under Mersereau, the RC underwent its second review in 1976. The committee concluded that the RC was financially, academically, and philosophically viable. Mersereau was appointed as full-time director and was able to direct substantially more time to administration than any of the earlier directors. During Mersereau's tenure, the RC/LS&A Joint Board instituted triennial curriculum reviews of each of the RC's programs, reviewed and recommended appointments and promotions, and served as a lobbying force within the LS&A Executive Committee. Elizabeth Douvan was director beginning July 1, 1985, followed by Herbert Eagle in May 1988, Thomas Weisskopf July 1996, and Charles Bright in 2005, and Angela Dillard in 2011.
Residential College Directors
1967 Burton Thuma
1967-1973 James Robertson
1973-1974 Louis Orlin
1974-1977 Marc Ross
1977-1985 John Mersereau, Jr.
1985-1988 Elizabeth Douvan
1988-1996 Herbert Eagle
1996-2005 Thomas Weisskopf
2005-2011 Charles Bright
2011-2014 Angela Dillard
The records of the Residential College relate to the planning and founding of the Residential College, 1962-1967, and include materials concerning curriculum, educational policies, governance and student attitudes from the College’s opening in 1967 through to the present. Research papers produced by the Social Science Program’s Student-Faculty Research Communities are also present. The records are arranged into the following series: Planning and Organization, Administration, Executive Committee, Triennial Reviews, Social Science Program, Photographs, Topical Files, Audiovisual, and Archived Website.
Subjects:
Education--Michigan.; Bryant Neighborhood (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Black Action Movement (University of Michigan); Graduate Employees Organization (University of Michigan); Northside Neighborhood (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Prisons--Michigan.; State Prison of Southern Michigan.; University of Michigan--Faculty.Faculty.; University of Michigan--Research.Research.; University of Michigan--Students.Students.; Women--Michigan.; Public schools--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan. Residential College.; Robertson, James H. (James Holman), 1915-; University of Michigan. College of Literature, Science, and the Arts.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1971-1980.StudentsSocial life and customs1971-1980.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1981-1990.StudentsSocial life and customs1981-1990.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
University of Michigan. Residential College.; Congress of Racial Equality. Detroit (Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Planning and Organization, 1962-1969
  The Planning and Organization series (2.3 linear feet, 1962-1970), relates to the conception and planning of the Residential College, including documents produced by the Faculty Planning Committee and personal files of Dean Burton Thuma related to the RC. The reports produced by the planning committee in 1965 and 1966 (referred to in the historical note above) are not in this series, but rather are in the Residential College Publications record group. Further information on the Planning and Organization can also be found in the Topical Files.
  - Architect Meeting Conference Notes, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Architectural Plans, 1964-1966 (Box 14)
  - Articles Establishing the Administrative Relation of the Residential College to the College of LS&A, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Brochures, 1965-1968 (Box 1)
  - Brochure Inquiries, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Building Committee, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Building Project - Miscellaneous Issues, 1966-1970 (Box 14)
  - Buildings -General, 1964-1966 (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Financing, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Cluster College Concept Conference, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Co-ops, 1962-1966 (Box 14)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1962-1967 (Box 1)
  - Danforth Foundation Workshop, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Dean of LS&A, 1964-1968 (Box 1)
  - Dining Commons, 1964-1966 (Box 14)
  - East Quad, 1965-1967 (Box 14)
  - "Event Shaping the Beginning of the UM's residential College" (as remembered by Max Heirich), undated (Box 14)
  - Faculty, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Planning Committee
    - Minutes, 1964-1967 (Box 1)
    - Reports, 1958-1967; undated; 6 folders (Box 1)
  - Foreign Language, 1964-1967 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Seminar, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
  - General, 1963-1966; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Historical Document on Establishing of RC (inclusing Committee on New College and Residential College Committee Materials), 1962-1963, undated; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Language Houses, 1964-1967 (Box 14)
  - Main Lounge Report, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Minutes (Construction), 1966-1970 (Box 14)
  - Newcomb, Theodore M., 1964-1967 (Box 1)
  - Office Building, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Organizational Chart, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Phase II Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
  - Planning Documents - General, 1964-1966 (Box 14)
  - Press, 1962-1969 (Box 1)
  - Proceedings, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Regents, 1966-1968 (Box 15)
  - Residence Hall Specifications, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Residence Halls - Type A, 1964-1966 (Box 15)
  - Residence Halls - Type B, 1964-1966 (Box 15)
  - Science Building, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Seminar - Urban Poverty, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Space Requirements, 1964-1966, undated (Box 15)
  - Student Advisory Committee, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Student Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Summary of Present Status of New College Plan, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Theatre, 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Thuma, Burton D., 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Thuma, Burton D.--Personal, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 2)
- Administration
  The Administration series (6.5 linear feet, 3.7 GB (online), 1966-2010), is organized chronologically by directorships of the Residential College, beginning in 1967, as follows: James Robertson, Louis Orlin, Marc Ross, John Mersereau, Elizabeth Douvan, Herbert Eagle, Thomas Weisskopf, and Charles Bright. The records relate to curriculum, governance, student attitudes, educational policies, and campus events. Digital content (3.7 GB) includes Director Charles Bright's e-mail files, which are arranged by subject and give a day-by-day account of the activities and contacts involved in directing the college. Some of the subjects of these files include admissions, community outreach, East Quad, and business relating to the various RC programs. These files are closed for 75 years from the date of creation under the student educational records restriction. Further information on the Administration can also be found in the Topical Files.
  - James Robertson Administration
    - Administrative Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 15)
    - Agenda Steering Committee -A Review of the Committee of the Residential College, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Assessment Committee Evaluation of RC, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Assessment Committee Minutes, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
    - Curriculum--Graduation Requirements, 1969-1972; undated (Box 2)
    - East Quadrangle Council Minutes, September 14, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Evaluations, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes [incomplete], 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Meeting and Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 15)
    - Faculty-Student Meetings, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Heirich, Max (Associate Director for Curriculum), 1973; undated (Box 15)
    - Housing Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 2)
    - LS&A Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2)
    - LSA Faculty Meeting re: RC, October 1972 (Box 15)
    - LSA Guidelines for RC, 1972 (Box 15)
    - New Academic Man Conference, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Programs
      - Behavioral Science, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
      - Concentrations, General, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
      - Foreign Language, 1967-1970; 3 folders (Box 2)
      - Freshman Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
      - History of Ideas, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
      - Philosophy, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
      - Science, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Orientation Schedule, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Representative Assembly, 1968-1971; 6 folders (Box 15)
    - Representative Assembly, 1971-1973; 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Representative Assembly, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - State of the Residential College Address, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Surveys
      - Class of 1971 Survey, 1971 (Box 2)
      - Class of 1974 Survey--RC Study Group Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
      - Heffernan Grant Proposal, 1970 (Box 2)
      - Pass-Fail Grading, 1969 (Box 2)
      - "A Student's Time,", circa 1969 (Box 2)
      - "The University of Michigan's Residential College,", 1971 (Box 2)
    - Teach-in, 1968-1970 (Box 16)
    - Teaching Certification, 1967-1971 (Box 16)
    - Urban Studies, 1968-1974 (Box 16)
  - Louis Orlin Administration
    - Orlin, Louis, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Marc Ross Administration
    - Admissions, 1966-1977; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Concentrations, 1974-1977 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Guide, 1976; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Evaluation of Residential College by College of Literature, Science and the Arts (LSA), 1974-1977; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Field Studies Program Report, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
    - Freshman Seminar Evaluation, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Goals of the Residential College, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Grading Policies, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
    - Outside Evaluations, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Program Evaluation, 1973-1976 (Box 16)
    - Proposals and Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
    - Representative Assembly, 1974-1977; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Social Science Program, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Working Paper - The Residential College in 1974: Suggestions for Some Directions, 1975 (Box 16)
  - John Mersereau Administration
    - Academic Evaluations, 1979-1982 (Box 3)
    - Admissions, 1979-1982 (Box 3)
    - Alumni, 1978 (Box 3)
    - "Between Two Worlds: The Residential College at the University of Michigan" by Marlene Hathaway, 1980 (Box 3)
    - College Night Lecture Series, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Committee of Curricular and Educational Policies, 1975-1978 (Box 3)
    - Counseling Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 3)
    - Counseling Handouts, 1978-1982 (Box 3)
    - East Quad Representative Assembly
      - Constitution, circa 1977 (Box 3)
      - Minutes, 1977-1984; 5 folders (Box 3)
    - Ex-Oriente Lux/Ex Olympo Newsletters and Calendars of Events, 1979-1985 (Box 19)
    - Faculty, 1979-1982 (Box 3)
    - Faculty Meetings and Correspodence, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Grading policies, 1979-1985 (Box 3)
    - Graduate Survey Reports, 1976-1981 (Box 16)
    - Intensive Language Conference, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Joint Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - "Liberal Arts in a Residential College,", 1982 (Box 3)
    - Mersereau, John, 1977-1985 (Box 3)
    - Orientation, 1977-1983; 5 folders (Box 3)
    - Programs
      - Concentrations, 1977-1982 (Box 3)
      - French, 1975-1985 (Box 3)
      - German, 1974-1985 (Box 3)
      - Language, 1975-1985 (Box 3)
      - Social Sciences, 1978-1984 (Box 16)
      - Spanish, 1976-1984 (Box 3)
    - Program Evaluation Material, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - Residential College Justification, 1974-1984 (Box 3)
    - Residential College Report, 1977-1981 (Box 16)
    - RC/LS&A Joint Board Program Evaluations, 1979-1984 (Box 3)
    - "The Speech of the Place: An Oral History of the Residential College, the First Fifteen Years", 1982 (Box 16)
    - Survey Results Graduate Classes of, 1975; 1976; 1980 (Box 3)
    - Talks at Commencement, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Elizabeth Douvan Administration
    - Anthropology Position Request, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Changes at the RC, 1985-1988 Report (Box 16)
    - Exxon Grant Proposal, 1987 (Box 3)
    - General Review of Residential College, 1985-1986 (Box 16)
    - Undergraduate Initiative Fund Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
    - Undergraduate Initiative Fund Proposal, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Herbert Eagle Administration
    - Academic Counseling Material, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
    - Eagle, Herbert, 1990-1996 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
    - French Program, Sylvie Carduner, 1989-1995 (Box 4)
    - Persian Gulf War Teach-in, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Report of the LS&A/RC Liaison Committee (Box 4)
    - Report of the LS&A/RC Liaison Committee on Creative Arts (Box 4)
    - Statistics, 1991-1993 (Box 16)
    - Survey of Current RC and East Quadrangle students, circa 1995 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Weisskopf Administration
    - Administrative Review, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Advisory Committee, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Artist in Residence Guidelines, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Benzinger Library, 2002-2005 (Box 17)
    - Budget
      - Fiscal Year, 2005; 2004-2005 (Box 17)
      - Fiscal Year, 2006; 2004-2005 (Box 17)
    - Community Outreach, 2002-2003 (Box 17)
    - Diversity, 1997-1999 (Box 17)
    - East Quad Renovation, 2004 (Box 17)
    - External Relations Task Force Report, 1999 (Box 17)
    - External Review Committee, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Facilities, 1998-2005; undated (Box 17)
    - Fundraising, 1997-1998 (Box 17)
    - Lecturers, 1995-2006 (Box 17)
    - Long Range Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 17)
    - Multiculturalism at RC seminar, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Multiculturalism at RC seminar, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Parents Weekend, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Personnel, 1991-1997 (Box 17)
    - Programs
      - Arts, 2002-2004 (Box 17)
      - Arts and Ideas, 2001 undated (Box 17)
      - Creative Writing, 2002-2004 (Box 17)
      - First Year Seminar (FYS), 2003-2004 (Box 17)
      - French, 2004 (Box 17)
      - German, 2002-2004 (Box 17)
      - Language (General), 2002-2005 (Box 17)
      - Latin, 2000 (Box 17)
      - Russian, 2002 (Box 17)
      - Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 2001-2006 (Box 17)
      - Spanish, 1997-2003 (Box 31)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2078 ]
    - Student Government, 2002-2005 (Box 17)
    - Thirtieth Anniversary Display Materials (miscellaneous items relating to RC history used for 30th anniversary in 1997) (Box 4)
    - Tracking RC Students, 1997-2001 (Box 17)
    - Transition to Grades Research Project, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Urban Community Studies Position, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
    - Website, 2001-2005 (Box 17)
  - Charles Bright Administration
    - Admissions Revise, 2009 (Box 17)
    - Advisory Committee (RCAC), 2005-2007 (Box 17)
    - Anniversary (40th), 1969-2007; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Arts of Citizenship, 2002-2009 (Box 18)
    - Arts on Earth, 2009-2010 (Box 18)
    - Assessment, 2008 (Box 18)
    - Budget, 2005-2010; 7 folders (Box 18)
    - Campus Compact, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Cheiniouk, Anatoli, undated (Box 18)
    - Convocation, 2006-2010 (Box 18)
    - Crime and Justice Minor, undated (Box 18)
    - Demographics, 2010 (Box 18)
    - Detroit Center, 2006-2010 (Box 18)
    - Development, 2005-2008; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Development Program Talking Points, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Directing News, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Email Correspondence, 2001-2011; .ZIP file)
      [SR Restricted until July 1, 2086 ]
    - Engagement, 2008 (Box 18)
    - Enrollments, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Meeting, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Faculty Retreats, 2007-2010; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Francis, Rick, 2006-2008; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Full-Time Equivalent (FTE) Levels, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Gala, 2009 (Box 18)
    - Gelman, Susan, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Gift Funds, 2007 (Box 18)
    - Graduation, 2009 (Box 18)
    - International Studies, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Hanlon, Phil, 2010 (Box 18)
    - Key Performance Indicators (KPI), 2005-2008 (Box 18)
    - McDonald, Terrence, 2006-2007 (Box 18)
    - Michigan Learning Community (MLC)-Co-location, 2010 (Box 18)
    - Michigan Learning Community-Proposal, 2007 (Box 18)
    - Monsaingeon, Bruno, 2006-2008 (Box 18)
    - Programs
      - Chinese, 2007 (Box 18)
      - Music, 2003-2006 (Box 31)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2036 ]
      - Science, 1984-2006; undated (Box 18)
      - Social Science, 1974-2007 (Box 18)
    - Semester in Detroit, 2008-2009 (Box 19)
    - Senior Dinner, 2004-2010; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Senior Seminar, 2006 (Box 19)
    - Spanish Language Internship Program (SLIP), 2008 (Box 19)
    - Theater Project, 2008-2009 (Box 19)
    - Turnley, Peter-Artist in Residence, 2006-2007 (Box 19)
    - Undergraduate Departmental Awards, 2009-2010 (Box 19)
    - Undergraduate Education, 2006-2010 (Box 19)
    - Urban Studies, 2009-2010 (Box 19)
    - Visiting Artists, 2009 (Box 19)
    - Website Work, 2008 (Box 19)
- Executive Committee
  The Executive Committee series (2 linear feet, 1971-2007), is organized chronologically and consists primarily of minutes, correspondence, and reports. The Committee was created on the recommendation of Director James Robertson, to assist the director with personnel and budgetary decisions, and initially consisted of three faculty and two students.
  - 1971-1986, 7 folders (Box 26)
  - 1986-1997, 2006-2007; 6 folders (Box 27)
- Triennial Reviews, 1977-1995
  The Triennial Reviews series (0.4 linear feet, 1977-1995), consists of reports evaluating RC programs, including topics such as course offerings, concentration requirements, personnel and enrollment information. Further information on the Administration can also be found in the Topical Files.
  - Freshman Seminars, 1979 (Box 4)
  - German Program, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Social Science Program, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Fine Arts Program, 1981 (Box 4)
  - French Program, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Spanish Program, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Arts and Ideas Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Creative Writing Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Drama Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Field Studies Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - German Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Literature Concentration, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Science Program, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Arts and Ideas Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Creative Writing, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Drama Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - French Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Fine Arts Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Language Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Social Science Program, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Drama Concentration, 1992 (Box 4)
  - First Year Seminar, 1995 (Box 4)
- Social Science Program, 1976-1991
  The Social Science Program series (1.0 linear foot, 1976-1991) consists of two subseries, Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE), and Student-Faculty Research Community. The FIPSE subseries contains the conceptual documents for the Student-Faculty Research Community, an educational innovation that proposed a seminar in which students and faculty members would collaborate on a social science research project, as presented in a FIPSE grant proposal. The Student-Faculty Research Community subseries contains the research reports produced by the RC social science seminars. The research reports are arranged in chronological order. Further information on the Administration can also be found in the Topical Files.
  - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education (FIPSE)
    - Chicago Meeting, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Meeting Agendas (Fall Planning), 1976 (Box 4)
    - Model Projects for Curriculum Committee, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Grant Proposal, circa 1976 (Box 4)
    - Minutes of Coordinating Committee Meetings, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003-2004 (Box 20)
  - Student-Faculty Research Community
    - Budget and Fundraising, 1984-1987 (Box 20)
    - Coordinating Committee, 1985-1987; undated; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Evaluations, 1985 (Box 31)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2060 ]
    - General, 1975-1978; undated (Box 20)
    - Recruitment and Publicity, 1984-1987 (Box 20)
    - Reports
      - "Issues in transition during the day care day: Interventions, controls and agendas,", undated (Box 4)
      - "Nurse practitioners in pediatrics and family planning: Prognosis positive?", undated (Box 4)
      - "Women, hard drugs and natural highs,", 1978 (Box 4)